fashionmonitor.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy & Cookies Policy

## Centaur Media PLC - Privacy & Cookies Policy

### 1\. SCOPE

This policy applies to personal information collected on websites owned or controlled by Centaur Communications Limited and its UK affiliates and their brands (for a list of these brands, please see http://www.centaurmedia.com/brands) (collectively referred to in this policy as “we”, "us" or "our").

We comply with data protection legislation such as the Data Protection Act 1998. This regulates the processing of personal data relating to you and grants you various rights in respect of your personal data.

The aim of this policy is to tell you how we will use any personal information we collect or you provide through our websites. Please read it carefully before you proceed. The data controller in respect of this website is Centaur Communications Limited.

### 2\. WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

You do not have to give us any personal information in order to use most of this website.

However, if you wish to register on this website, subscribe to a service, book delegate space at events, request further information, or provide content for inclusion on this website (e.g. blogs or other online forums)we may collect the following personal information from you:

  * name, address, phone number and email address; and
  * gender, salary, employment details, employer details, and education details.

We will also keep a record of any financial transaction you make with us but we do not directly collect, process or store your debit or credit card information. Online payments made through this website are processed securely by a third party payment provider Datacash. Please refer to Datacash's Privacy Policy www.datacash.com/mcdatacash/privacy/privacy.html for how your payment card data is processed by them.

You may also choose to provide additional voluntary information in the course of your use of this website.

In addition, we may automatically collect information about the website that you came from or are going to. We also collect information about the pages of this website which you visit, IP addresses, the type of browser you use and the times you access this website. However, this information is aggregated and is not used to identify you.

### 3\. HOW WILL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION BE USED AND SHARED?

The personal information we collect allows us to:

  * provide the products and services you have ordered;
  * verify your identity and details of your payment method or credit card amount;
  * administer our website and provide customer services;
  * meet legal, regulatory and compliance requirements;
  * monitor and analyse the use of any account to prevent, investigate and/or report fraud, terrorism, misrepresentation, security incidents or crime;
  * gather management information to form statistical and trend analysis;
  * communicate with you;
  * investigate any complaints about this website;
  * personalise your experience of this website; and
  * contact you about our products and services which we think might be of interest to you (where we have the appropriate permissions to do so; please see Paragraph 5 for more information).

We may share your personal information with all of our affiliate companies and their brands for the above purposes.

We may employ the services of third party service providers to help us in certain areas, such as website hosting, maintenance, call centre operation. In some cases the third party may receive your information. However, at all times, we will control and be responsible for the use of your information.

We may use aggregated information so we can administer and improve our website, analyse trends, gather broad demographic information and detect suspicious or fraudulent transactions. We may pass this information to third parties.

If you provide a credit or debit card, we may also use third parties to check the validity of the sort code, account number and card number you submit in order to prevent fraud as well as to process any transaction you attempt via the website.

If false or inaccurate information is provided and fraud is identified, details will be passed to fraud prevention agencies. Law enforcement agencies may access and use this information. We and other organisations may also access and use this information to prevent fraud and money laundering, for example when:

  * checking details in applications for credit and credit related or other facilities
  * managing credit and credit related accounts or facilities
  * recovering debt
  * checking details on proposals and claims for all types of insurance
  * checking details of job applicants and employees.

Please email us on customerdata@centaurmedia.com if you want to have details of those fraud prevention agencies from whom we obtain and to whom we pass information about you. You have a legal right to these details.

### 4\. TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION OUTSIDE THE EEA

We may transfer some of your personal information to the United States of America and to Singapore as we have affiliates in both these jurisdictions. These countries may not have equivalent data protection legislation to the UK. However, when we transfer your personal information in this way, we will keep it securely and only use it as outlined in this Privacy & Cookies Policy. By submitting your personal information to this website, you consent to such transfers taking place.

### 5\. MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

Where you have given us the appropriate permissions during the registration process to the website/website services (as applicable), we may from time to time contact you by email, SMS, telephone or post about our products and services (including from all our brands) that may be of interest to you.

If at any point, you would like to opt-out of receiving such marketing communications from us, or would like to change the channels that we use to contact you, please click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any emails you receive, or email us, stating your preferences, at customerdata@centaurmedia.com.

### 6\. COOKIES AND RELATED TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

#### 6.1 Use of Cookies on our website

We use cookies to collect information about store your online preference. Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser which allows the server to uniquely identify the browser on each page.

We use the following categories of cookies on our website:

##### Strictly Necessary Cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features. Without these cookies, services you have asked for such as remembering your login details or shopping basket items cannot be provided.

##### Performance Cookies

These cookies collect anonymous information on how people use our website. For example, we use Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve areas such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.

##### Functionality Cookies

These cookies remember choices you make such as the country you visit our website from, language and search parameters such as size, colour or product line. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate to your selections and to make the visits more tailored and pleasant. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.

##### Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies

These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert as well as help measure the effectiveness of an advertising campaign. The cookies are usually placed by third party advertising networks. They remember the websites you visit and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers.

##### Social Media Cookies

These cookies allow you to share what you’ve been doing on the website on social media such as Facebook and Twitter. These cookies are not within our control. Please refer to the respective privacy policies for how their cookies work.

If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the help and support area on your internet browser for instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies.

Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site. To find out more about cookies please visit: www.allaboutcookies.org or see www.youronlinechoices.eu which contains further information about behavioural advertising and online privacy.

#### 6.2 Use of Web Beacons.

Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information which including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign.

### 7\. LINKS

Our site contains links to other websites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to link from this site. We encourage use to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your personal information.

### 8\. SECURITY

We have implemented reasonable technical and organisational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorised access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

### 9\. SALE OF THE BUSINESS

In the event that the business is sold or integrated with another business, your details will be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchaser’s adviser and will be passed to the new owners of the business.

### 10\. ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You are entitled to see the personal information held about you. If you wish to do this, please contact us at customerdata@centaurmedia.com. We may require you to provide verification of your identity and to pay an administration fee (which is currently £10) to provide a copy of the personal information we hold. Please note that in certain circumstances we may withhold access to your personal information where we have the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

### 11\. UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You may review, correct, update or change your personal information at any time by contacting us at customerdata@centaurmedia.com.

### 12\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY & COOKIES POLICY

If our Privacy & Cookies Policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

### 13\. HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this statement or your personal information, please contact us at customerdata@centaurmedia.com.
